gorealdose.com 2015-12-19

# Privacy Policy

### **Privacy Policy**

**HOW WE PROTECT YOUR PRIVACY** This privacy policy applies to http://www.doubleyourfatlossnow.com and http://gorealdose.com owned and operated by RealDose Nutrition LLC. This privacy policy tells you how we collect, use, and protect your personal information. By visiting our websites www.gorealdose.com and www.doubleyourfatlossnow.com, you accept and agree to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy. In particular, you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this privacy policy. 

RealDose Nutrition LLC has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program covers the sites www.gorealdose.com and www.doubleyourfatlossnow.com. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [contactus@gorealdose.com](mailto:contactus@gorealdose.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request).

**MINORS**

We do not provide services or sell products to children. If you are below the age of 18, you may use our website only with the permission and active involvement of a parent or legal guardian. If you are a minor under 13, please do not provide us or other website visitors with any personal information. 

**POLICY IS PART OF OUR TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE**

Our privacy policy is part of, and subject to, our website's terms and conditions of use. You may view these terms and conditions on our website.

**THE TYPE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOU**

Like most places on the Internet, simply by visiting our website you automatically tell us certain information. This includes basic information such as your IP address, when you visited, the website from where you came prior to visiting us, the website where you go when you leave our websites, your computer's operating system, and the type of web browser that you are using. Our websites automatically records this basic information about you and store it in log files.

We combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to offer special discounts and to improve marketing, analytics, and site functionality. 

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by RealDose Nutrition LLC and our marketing, advertising and support partners. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies for our shopping cart, for user authentication and for user settings. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited. 

**Flash LSOs**

We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as Flash to store [content information and preferences.] Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as HTML 5 to collect and store information.

Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. To manage Flash LSOs please [click here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html). 

**Behavioral Targeting / Re-Targeting**

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

We may also collect any data that you provide us by posting it at our websites (through our contact us page) or by e-mail (such as your name and email address). You can always choose not to provide us with information. However, if you do withhold information, we may deny you access to some or all of our website's services and features. 

Any information provided on our website order forms is collected by our payment processing service providers on their servers from Customers who access our site. That information is then shared with RealDose. This information includes ordering information such as shipping and billing names and addresses, phone numbers, email address, and credit card information (See "Orders" below). We use this information primarily to fulfill customer orders and requests. We do not share this information with any third parties. However, we may disclose personal information collected if we have received your permission beforehand or in very special circumstances, such as when we believe that such disclosure is required by law or other special cases described below. 

**ORDERS AND USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personal information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card information and expiration date). We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. 

You may also provide personal information about other people, such as their name and email address. This information is only used for the sole purpose of completing your request or for whatever reason it may have been provided

**CONTACT US**

We will communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes. 

**WHAT WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION**

We use your information to operate our website's business activities. For example, we may use this data to contact you about changes to our websites, new services, or special offers, resolve disputes, troubleshoot issues, bill you for goods, and enforce our website's terms and conditions.

As a general rule, we will not share, sell, rent or trade your data with third parties without your permission. However, there are some important exceptions to this rule that are described in the following paragraphs. 

We may, in our sole discretion, provide information about you as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site or other government officials for purposes of fraud investigations, alleged intellectual property infringement, or any other suspected illegal activity or matters that may expose us to legal liability. 

Although we do not disclose individually identifiable information, we may disclose aggregate data about our website's visitors to advertisers or other third parties for marketing and promotional purposes. 

From time to time, we may use third party suppliers to provide services on our website such as credit card processing to bill you for goods and shipping companies to fulfill orders. We restrict the way third party suppliers can use your information. They are not allowed to sell or give your information to others. We will share personal information as necessary for that third party to provide that service. 

In the event that we go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personal information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email and/or prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. 

**ARTICLES**

Our Web site offers publicly accessible articles. You should be aware that any information you provide while leaving comments within this area of our site may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our articles, contact us at [contactus@gorealdose.com](mailto:contactus@gorealdose.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

**ACCESS TO PERSONAL INFORMATION**

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, amend, delete inaccuracies or deactivate it by contacting us at [contactus@gorealdose.com](mailto:contactus@gorealdose.com). We will respond to your access request within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [contactus@gorealdose.com](mailto:contactus@gorealdose.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

**AUTORESPONDERS**

We may use autoresponders to communicate with you by e-mail. To protect your privacy, we use a verified opt-in system for such communications and you can always opt-out of such communications using the links contained in each autoresponder message. If you have difficulties opting out, you may contact us by sending an e-mail to [contactus@gorealdose.com](mailto:contactus@gorealdose.com), or sending us mail to the address listed below. 

**OPTING-OUT**

We provide you the opportunity to opt-out from any promotional or marketing emails that we may send you. You may do so by following the instructions included in each communication or by emailing us at [contactus@gorealdose.com](mailto:contactus@gorealdose.com). 

**SECURITY**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on order forms that are hosted by our third party service providers, the transmission of that information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

**Links to Other Sites**

Our Web sites contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware, that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy policies of each and every Web site that collects personal information. 

This privacy policy applies only to information collected by our Web sites. 

**Testimonials**

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [contactus@gorealdose.com](mailto:contactus@gorealdose.com). 

**Social Media Features and Widgets**

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

**Import Contacts**

You can import contacts from your Outlook or other email account address book to invite them to become members of our site. We collect the username and password for the email account you wish to import your contacts from and will only use it for that purpose. 

**POLICY CHANGES**

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

Any questions or concerns about this policy should be brought to our attention by sending an e-mail to [contactus@gorealdose.com](mailto:contactus@gorealdose.com) and providing us with information relating to your concern. 

You may also mail your concerns to us at the following address:  
RealDose Nutrition LLC  
1942 Broadway  
Suite 314   
Boulder, CO 80302 

**CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

If you are a California resident and our customer, Cal. Civ. Code 1798.83 permits you to request certain information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To request this information, please send an e-mail to [contactus@gorealdose.com](mailto:contactus@gorealdose.com) or write us at the following address:  
RealDose Nutrition LLC  
1942 Broadway  
Suite 314   
Boulder, CO 80302  
United States 

This privacy policy was last updated on 11-05-2014.
